<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="transform.xsl"?>
<movie_list version="0.0">
    <movie>
        <name>Wreck-It Ralph</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzMxNTExOTkyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzEyNDc0OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.800000190734863</score>
        <duration>108 min</duration>
        <launchDate>2 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Animation</genre>
            <genre>Adventure</genre>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Rich Moore</director>
        <stars>
            <star>John C. Reilly</star>
            <star>Jack McBrayer</star>
            <star>Jane Lynch</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Wreck-It Ralph longs to be as beloved as his game's perfect Good Guy, Fix-It Felix. Problem is, nobody loves a Bad Guy. But they do love heroes... so when a modern, first-person shooter game arrives featuring tough-as-nails Sergeant Calhoun, Ralph sees it as his ticket to heroism and happiness. He sneaks into the game with a simple plan -- win a medal -- but soon wrecks everything, and accidentally unleashes a deadly enemy that threatens every game in the arcade. Ralph's only hope? Vanellope von Schweetz, a young troublemaking "glitch" from a candy-coated cart racing game who might just be the one to teach Ralph what it means to be a Good Guy. But will he realize he is good enough to become a hero before it's "Game Over" for the entire arcade? Written by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>The Man with the Iron Fists</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5ODI3ODkzOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTQxNjUwOA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.400000095367432</score>
        <duration>95 min</duration>
        <launchDate>2 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Action</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>RZA</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Russell Crowe</star>
            <star>Cung Le</star>
            <star>Lucy Liu</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In Jungle Village, the leader of the Lion's clan Gold Lion is summoned by the Governor and assigned to protect his gold that will be transported through the village. However he is betrayed and murdered by the greedy Silver Lion and Bronze Lion. Gold Lion's favorite son Zen Yi, a.k.a. The X-Blade, seeks revenge and heads to Jungle Village, but he is defeated by Brass Body and rescued by the local Blacksmith Thaddeus. Meanwhile the Gemini Female and the Gemini Male protect the Governor's gold, but they are vanquished by the army of Silver and Bronze Lion. The Blacksmith is abducted by the Lions and has his arms severed by Brass Body. However he is saved by the British Jack Knife, who is the emissary of the Emperor, and he manufactures iron arms for Thaddeus. Meanwhile the Governor sends the Jackal army to fight against the Lions and they hide the gold in the brothel of Madam Blossom. However, Madam Blossom and his girls form an army of black widows and together with Jack, Zen Yi and The... Written by Claudio Carvalho, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Flight</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxMjI1OTMxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjc3NTY1OA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.300000190734863</score>
        <duration>138 min</duration>
        <launchDate>2 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Robert Zemeckis</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Denzel Washington</star>
            <star>Nadine Velazquez</star>
            <star>Don Cheadle</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Whip Whitaker is a commuter airline pilot. While on a flight from Orlando to Atlanta something goes wrong and the plane starts to fly erratically. With little choice Whip crashes the plane and saves almost all on board. When he wakes up in the hospital, his friend from the airline union introduces him to a lawyer who tells him there's a chance he could face criminal charges because his blood test reveals that he is intoxicated with alcohol and cocaine. He denies being impaired, so while an investigation is underway, he is told to keep his act together. However, letting go of his addiction is not as easy as it seems... Written by Immanuel Ambhara</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Este é o Meu Lugar</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUzMDg5NjM3Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTQ3NTI2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.599999904632568</score>
        <duration>118 min</duration>
        <launchDate>25 April 2012 (Portugal)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Paolo Sorrentino</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Sean Penn</star>
            <star>Frances McDormand</star>
            <star>Judd Hirsch</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Cheyenne, a wealthy former rock star (Penn), now bored and jaded in his retirement embarks on a quest to find his father's persecutor, an ex-Nazi war criminal now hiding out in the U.S. Learning his father is close to death, he travels to New York in the hope of being reconciled with him during his final hours, only to arrive too late. Having been estranged for over 30 years, it is only now in death that he learns the true extent of his father's humiliation in Auschwitz at the hands of former SS Officer Aloise Lange - an event he is determined to avenge. So begins a life-altering journey across the heartland of America to track down and confront his father's nemesis. As his quest unfolds, Cheyenne is reawakened by the people he encounters and his journey is transformed into one of reconciliation and self discovery. As his date with destiny arrives and he tracks down Lange, Cheyenne must finally decide if it is redemption he seeks ....or revenge. Starring two time Academy Award winner ... Written by Anonymous</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>A Late Quartet</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM3MDc3MzIzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjkwNTU0OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.900000095367432</score>
        <duration>105 min</duration>
        <launchDate>10 October 2013 (Portugal)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Music</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Yaron Zilberman</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Philip Seymour Hoffman</star>
            <star>Christopher Walken</star>
            <star>Catherine Keener</star>
        </stars>
        <description>After a classical string quartet's 25 years of success, Peter, the cellist and oldest member, decides that he must retire when he learns he has Parkinson's Disease. For the others, that announcement proves a catalyst for letting their hidden resentments come to the surface while the married members' daughter has disruptive desires of her own. All this threatens to tear the group apart even as they are famous for playing Beethoven's String Quartet No. 14, opus 131, a piece that is played non-stop no matter how life interferes. Written by Kenneth Chisholm (kchishol@rogers.com)</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>The Details</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1MDcyNDIyNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzc3MTc1OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.099999904632568</score>
        <duration>91 min</duration>
        <launchDate>January 2011 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Jacob Aaron Estes</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Tobey Maguire</star>
            <star>Elizabeth Banks</star>
            <star>Laura Linney</star>
        </stars>
        <description>When a family of raccoons discover worms living underneath the sod in Jeff and Nealy's backyard, this pest problem begins a darkly comic and wild chain reaction of domestic tension, infidelity and murder.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Jack and Diane</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ5MDEyNDk5MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjMxODk2Nw@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>4.199999809265137</score>
        <duration>110 min</duration>
        <launchDate>20 April 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Horror</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Bradley Rust Gray</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Riley Keough</star>
            <star>Juno Temple</star>
            <star>Kylie Minogue</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Jack and Diane, two teenage girls, meet in New York City and spend the night kissing ferociously. Diane's charming innocence quickly begins to open Jack's tough skinned heart. But, when Jack discovers that Diane is leaving the country in a week she tries to push her away. Diane must struggle to keep their love alive while hiding the secret that her newly awakened sexual desire is giving her werewolf-like visions. Written by filmsalt.com</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Vamps</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg0ODkwMzI0NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDc4OTc2OA@@._V1_SY317_CR6,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>4.900000095367432</score>
        <duration>92 min</duration>
        <launchDate>2 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
            <genre>Horror</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Amy Heckerling</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Alicia Silverstone</star>
            <star>Krysten Ritter</star>
            <star>Larry Wilmore</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In Manhattan, the vampires Goody and Stacy share an apartment and work and study in the night-shift. Goody was turned in vampire in 1840 by the evil Cisserus, who turned Stacy in the 90s, and they became best friends but Goody never told her real age to her friend. They only drink mice blood and refuse to drink human blood, and they go together to the Vampire Anonymous. Stacy falls in love with her classmate Joey, and soon she learns that he is the son of the vampire slayer Dr. Van Helsing. Meanwhile, Goody meets her former passion, Danny, in the hospital where his wife is terminal. When Stacy gets pregnant, Goody knows that the only way that the child can survive is killing Cisserus, since they would revert to their human ages. But nobody knows here her lair is. Written by Claudio Carvalho, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>High Ground</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4MDI2Nzg0Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTQ2NjU2OA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>4.199999809265137</score>
        <duration>92 min</duration>
        <launchDate>April 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Documentary</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Michael Brown</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Steve Baskis</star>
            <star>Dan Sidles</star>
            <star>Katherine Ragazzino</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Eleven veterans returning from Iraq and Afghanistan join an expedition to climb the 20,000 foot Himalayan giant Mount Lobuche. With blind adventurer Erik Weihenmayer and a team of Everest summiteers as their guides, they set out on an emotional and gripping climb to reach the top in an attempt to heal the emotional and physical wounds of the longest war in U.S. history. Representing nearly every branch of the military, the veterans, and the Gold Star Mom who joins their trek, bring humor and deep emotion to this hero's journey all captured with breathtaking, vertigo-inducing cinematography. Written by Khumbu Pictures, LLC</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Skyfall</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjM1MzMzOTA3MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTE3NzA1OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.800000190734863</score>
        <duration>143 min</duration>
        <launchDate>9 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Action</genre>
            <genre>Adventure</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Sam Mendes</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Daniel Craig</star>
            <star>Javier Bardem</star>
            <star>Naomie Harris</star>
        </stars>
        <description>When Bond's latest assignment goes gravely wrong and agents around the world are exposed, MI6 is attacked forcing M to relocate the agency. These events cause her authority and position to be challenged by Gareth Mallory (Ralph Fiennes), the new Chairman of the Intelligence and Security Committee. With MI6 now compromised from both inside and out, M is left with one ally she can trust: Bond. 007 takes to the shadows - aided only by field agent, Eve (Naomie Harris) - following a trail to the mysterious Silva (Javier Bardem), whose lethal and hidden motives have yet to reveal themselves. Written by JoaoBond</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Lincoln</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQzNzczMDUyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjM2ODEzOA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.5</score>
        <duration>150 min</duration>
        <launchDate>16 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Biography</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>History</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Steven Spielberg</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Daniel Day-Lewis</star>
            <star>Sally Field</star>
            <star>David Strathairn</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In 1865, as the American Civil War winds inexorably toward conclusion, U.S. president Abraham Lincoln endeavors to achieve passage of the landmark constitutional amendment which will forever ban slavery from the United States. However, his task is a race against time, for peace may come at any time, and if it comes before the amendment is passed, the returning southern states will stop it before it can become law. Lincoln must, by almost any means possible, obtain enough votes from a recalcitrant Congress before peace arrives and it is too late. Yet the president is torn, as an early peace would save thousands of lives. As the nation confronts its conscience over the freedom of its entire population, Lincoln faces his own crisis of conscience -- end slavery or end the war. Written by Jim Beaver &lt;jumblejim@prodigy.net&gt;</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>The Comedy</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA0OTA3ODU4M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDY3NTM1OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.099999904632568</score>
        <duration>95 min</duration>
        <launchDate>21 January 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Rick Alverson</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Tim Heidecker</star>
            <star>Eric Wareheim</star>
            <star>James Murphy</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Indifferent to the notion of inheriting his father's estate, a Williamsburg guy passes the time with his friends, playing games of mock sincerity and irreverence.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Dangerous Liaisons</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY0MDA5NDE4Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjM3MjMxOA@@._V1_SY317_CR5,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.300000190734863</score>
        <duration>110 min</duration>
        <launchDate>27 September 2012 (China)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Mystery</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Jin-ho Hur</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Cecilia Cheung</star>
            <star>Dong-gun Jang</star>
            <star>Ziyi Zhang</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In Shanghai, an aging socialite's infatuation with her ex-boyfriend manifests itself as a risky game, where her former lover agrees to seduce, then abandon a naive young woman.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>A Royal Affair</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3MDE4MTQ4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDgwNDYyOA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.5</score>
        <duration>137 min</duration>
        <launchDate>21 March 2013 (Portugal)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>History</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Nikolaj Arcel</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Alicia Vikander</star>
            <star>Mads Mikkelsen</star>
            <star>Mikkel Boe Følsgaard</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In 1767, the British Princess Caroline is betrothed to the mad King Christian VII of Denmark, but her life with the erratic monarch in the oppressive country becomes an isolating misery. However, Christian soon gains a fast companion with the German Dr. Johann Struensee, a quietly idealistic man of the Enlightenment. As the only one who can influence the King, Struensee is able to begin sweeping enlightened reforms of Denmark through Christian even as Caroline falls for the doctor. However, their secret affair proves a tragic mistake that their conservative enemies use to their advantage in a conflict that threatens to claim more than just the lovers as their victims. Written by Kenneth Chisholm (kchishol@rogers.com)</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Nature Calls</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM1NDE0NTI5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTY1MTY0OA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>3.799999952316284</score>
        <duration>79 min</duration>
        <launchDate>9 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Todd Rohal</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Patton Oswalt</star>
            <star>Johnny Knoxville</star>
            <star>Rob Riggle</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Polar-opposite brothers Randy and Kirk never saw eye-to-eye, but their rivalry is taken to a new level when Randy hijacks Kirk's son's sleepover, taking the boys on a Scout Trip to remember.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>In Their Skin</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTU3ODczMTcwMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzg1MTA3OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.199999809265137</score>
        <duration>97 min</duration>
        <launchDate>9 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Horror</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Jeremy Power Regimbal</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Selma Blair</star>
            <star>Joshua Close</star>
            <star>James D'Arcy</star>
        </stars>
        <description>After the accidental death of their six-year-old daughter, the Hughes family escape their busy upscale suburban life and head to their isolated cottage for some quality time. An evening with their friendly neighbors is suddenly interrupted when one mans obsession with perfection escalates into a violent struggle, forcing the families to go beyond what they ever thought they were capable of in order to survive. Written by Anonymous</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Starlet</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzI5NTI3MjYyNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTg1NjQ2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.5</score>
        <duration>103 min</duration>
        <launchDate>2 May 2013 (Hong Kong)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Sean Baker</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Dree Hemingway</star>
            <star>Besedka Johnson</star>
            <star>Boonee</star>
        </stars>
        <description>STARLET explores the unlikely cross-generational friendship between 21 year-old Jane (Dree Hemingway), and the elderly Sadie (Besedka Johnson), two women whose worlds collide in California's San Fernando Valley. Jane, an aspiring actress, spends her time getting high with her dysfunctional roommates, Melissa and Mikey (Stella Maeve and James Ransone), while caring for her Chihuahua, Starlet. Sadie, a widow, passes her days alone, tending to her flower garden. After a confrontation between the women at Sadie's yard sale, Jane uncovers a hidden stash of money inside a relic from Sadie's past. Jane attempts to befriend the caustic older woman in an effort to solve her dilemma and secrets emerge as their relationship grows. Director Sean Baker continues in the naturalistic style of his previous films, the award-winning and Spirit Award nominees PRINCE OF BROADWAY and TAKE OUT, capturing the rhythms of everyday life with an authenticity rarely seen in cinema. Featuring a pair of ... Written by anonymous</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 2</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTcyMzUyMzY1OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDQ4ODk1OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.5</score>
        <duration>115 min</duration>
        <launchDate>16 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Adventure</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Fantasy</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Bill Condon</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Kristen Stewart</star>
            <star>Robert Pattinson</star>
            <star>Taylor Lautner</star>
        </stars>
        <description>The final Twilight Saga begins with Bella now a vampire learning to use her abilities. And happy to see her daughter, Renesmee is flourishing. But when someone sees Renesmee do something that makes them think that she was turned. This person goes to the Volturi, because it is a violation to turn a child. And the penalty is death for both who turned the child into a vampire and the child, cause they deem a turned child too dangerous. Alice gets a vision of the Volturi coming after them. So the Cullens try to convince them that Renesmee is not a threat. So they ask friends and family to come stand with them. But when someone who has it in for the Volturi shows up and tells them they should be ready for a fight. And they get ready. Written by rcs0411@yahoo.com</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Anna Karenina</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTU0NDgxNDg0NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjE4MzkwOA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.599999904632568</score>
        <duration>129 min</duration>
        <launchDate>6 December 2012 (Portugal)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Joe Wright</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Keira Knightley</star>
            <star>Jude Law</star>
            <star>Aaron Taylor-Johnson</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In 1874, in the Imperial Russia, the aristocratic Anna Karenina travels from Saint Petersburg to Moscow to save the marriage of her brother Prince Oblonsky, who had had a love affair with his housemaid. Anna Karenina has a cold marriage with her husband, Count Alexei Karenin, and they have a son. Anna meets the cavalry officer Count Vronsky at the train station and they feel attracted by each other. Soon she learns that Vronsky will propose Kitty, who is the younger sister of her sister-in-law Dolly. Anna satisfactorily resolves the infidelity case of her brother and Kitty invites her to stay for the ball. However, Anna Karenina and Vronsky dance in the ball, calling the attention of the conservative society. Soon they have a love affair that will lead Anna Karenina to a tragic fate. Written by Claudio Carvalho, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Silver Linings Playbook</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM2MTI5NzA3MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODExNTc0OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.900000095367432</score>
        <duration>122 min</duration>
        <launchDate>25 December 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>David O. Russell</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Bradley Cooper</star>
            <star>Jennifer Lawrence</star>
            <star>Robert De Niro</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Against medical advice and without the knowledge of her husband Pat Solatano Sr., caring Dolores Solatano discharges her adult son, Pat Solatano Jr., from a Maryland mental health institution after his minimum eight month court ordered stint. The condition of the release includes Pat Jr. moving back in with his parents in their Philadelphia home. Although Pat Jr.'s institutionalization was due to him beating up the lover of his wife Nikki, he was diagnosed with bipolar disorder. Nikki has since left him and has received a restraining order against him. Although he is on medication (which he doesn't take because of the way it makes him feel) and has mandatory therapy sessions, Pat Jr. feels like he can manage on the outside solely by healthy living and looking for the "silver linings" in his life. His goals are to get his old job back as a substitute teacher, but more importantly reunite with Nikki. He finds there are certain instances where he doesn't cope well, however no less so ... Written by Huggo</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Lincoln</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQzNzczMDUyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjM2ODEzOA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.5</score>
        <duration>150 min</duration>
        <launchDate>16 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Biography</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>History</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Steven Spielberg</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Daniel Day-Lewis</star>
            <star>Sally Field</star>
            <star>David Strathairn</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In 1865, as the American Civil War winds inexorably toward conclusion, U.S. president Abraham Lincoln endeavors to achieve passage of the landmark constitutional amendment which will forever ban slavery from the United States. However, his task is a race against time, for peace may come at any time, and if it comes before the amendment is passed, the returning southern states will stop it before it can become law. Lincoln must, by almost any means possible, obtain enough votes from a recalcitrant Congress before peace arrives and it is too late. Yet the president is torn, as an early peace would save thousands of lives. As the nation confronts its conscience over the freedom of its entire population, Lincoln faces his own crisis of conscience -- end slavery or end the war. Written by Jim Beaver &lt;jumblejim@prodigy.net&gt;</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Jab Tak Hai Jaan</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUyMzM5OTM5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTIwMjA3OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.900000095367432</score>
        <duration>176 min</duration>
        <launchDate>13 November 2012 (India)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Yash Chopra</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Shah Rukh Khan</star>
            <star>Katrina Kaif</star>
            <star>Anushka Sharma</star>
        </stars>
        <description>A young immigrant falls in love with a NRI who wanted to marry any British person, not a typical brown Indian. But she falls in love with that young musician, but this love story ends with a breakup. Then that man, fed up with life with vast emotion joins Indian army bomb squad, where he flirts with death everyday. A young discovery channel journalist approaches his team to cover bomb squad story but falls in love with him. Written by dwa</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Price Check</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODI3NjkxNTEyN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzEwOTE2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.400000095367432</score>
        <duration>92 min</duration>
        <launchDate>25 January 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Michael Walker</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Parker Posey</star>
            <star>Eric Mabius</star>
            <star>Annie Parisse</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Pete Cozy is having trouble resolving a happy marriage and family life with rising debt and a job he hates. When his new boss, Susan, a human dynamo, shows up, Pete is pulled into the maelstrom that is her life and made to work harder than he ever has before. Suddenly, money and opportunities come his way, but at what price? Written by CA</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Citadel</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzIwMTQ2NTAyM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDIzMjQ0OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.300000190734863</score>
        <duration>84 min</duration>
        <launchDate>1 March 2013 (UK)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Horror</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Ciaran Foy</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Aneurin Barnard</star>
            <star>James Cosmo</star>
            <star>Wunmi Mosaku</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Tommy Cowley is a young father inflicted with chronic agoraphobia since his wife was brutally attacked by a gang of a twisted feral children. Trapped in the dilapidated suburbia of Edenstown, he finds himself terrorised by the same gang, who now seem intent on taking his baby daughter. Torn between the help of an understanding nurse and a vigilante priest, Tommy sets out to learn the nightmarish truth surrounding these hooded children. He also discovers that to be free of his fears, he must finally face the demons of his past and enter the one place that he fears the most - the abandoned tower block known as the Citadel. Written by Anonymous</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Life of Pi</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTg2OTY2ODg5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODM5MTYxOA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>8.100000381469727</score>
        <duration>127 min</duration>
        <launchDate>21 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Adventure</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Fantasy</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Ang Lee</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Suraj Sharma</star>
            <star>Irrfan Khan</star>
            <star>Adil Hussain</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In Canada, a writer visits the Indian storyteller Pi Patel and asks him to tell his life story. Pi tells the story of his childhood in Pondicherry, India, and the origin of his nickname. One day, his father, a zoo owner, explains that the municipality is no longer supporting the zoo and he has hence decided to move to Canada, where the animals the family owns would also be sold. They board on a Japanese cargo ship with the animals and out of the blue, there is a storm, followed by a shipwrecking. Pi survives in a lifeboat with a zebra, an orangutan, a hyena and a male Bengal tiger nicknamed Richard Parker. They are adrift in the Pacific Ocean, with aggressive hyena and Rickard Parker getting hungry. Pi needs to find a way to survive. Written by Claudio Carvalho, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Red Dawn</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjI0MDAwMzA1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzIxMjY3OA@@._V1_SY317_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.300000190734863</score>
        <duration>93 min</duration>
        <launchDate>21 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Action</genre>
            <genre>War</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Dan Bradley</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Chris Hemsworth</star>
            <star>Isabel Lucas</star>
            <star>Josh Hutcherson</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In Spokane, Washington, the population is awake by a North Korean invasion with paratroopers. The marine Jed Eckert and his brother Matt Eckert escape with a group of friends to an isolated cabin in the woods. They witness the cruel Captain Cho executing their father and they decide to form a resistance group named Wolverines fighting against the invaders. Written by Claudio Carvalho, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Rise of the Guardians</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkzMjgwMDg1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTgzNTI1OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.199999809265137</score>
        <duration>97 min</duration>
        <launchDate>21 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Animation</genre>
            <genre>Adventure</genre>
            <genre>Family</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Peter Ramsey</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Hugh Jackman</star>
            <star>Alec Baldwin</star>
            <star>Isla Fisher</star>
        </stars>
        <description>When an evil spirit known as Pitch lays down the gauntlet to take over the world, the immortal Guardians must join forces for the first time to protect the hopes, beliefs, and imaginations of children all over the world. Written by DreamWorks Animation</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Hitchcock</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODAwNDI5NjIwN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjc4ODc2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.900000095367432</score>
        <duration>98 min</duration>
        <launchDate>14 December 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Biography</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Sacha Gervasi</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Anthony Hopkins</star>
            <star>Helen Mirren</star>
            <star>Scarlett Johansson</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In 1959, Alfred Hitchcock and his wife, Alma, are at the top of their creative game as filmmakers amid disquieting insinuations about it being time to retire. To recapture his youth's artistic daring, Alfred decides his next film will adapt the lurid horror novel, Psycho, over everyone's misgivings. Unfortunately, as Alfred self-finances and labors on this film, Alma finally loses patience with his roving eye and controlling habits with his actresses. When an ambitious friend lures her to collaborate on a work of their own, the resulting marital tension colors Alfred's work even as the novel's inspiration haunts his dreams. Written by Kenneth Chisholm (kchishol@rogers.com)</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Rust and Bone</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTczMTU4NDUyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTM5NDY0OA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.5</score>
        <duration>120 min</duration>
        <launchDate>7 March 2013 (Portugal)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Jacques Audiard</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Marion Cotillard</star>
            <star>Matthias Schoenaerts</star>
            <star>Armand Verdure</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Put in charge of his young son, Alain leaves Belgium for Antibes to live with his sister and her husband as a family. Alain's bond with Stephanie, a killer whale trainer, grows deeper after Stephanie suffers a horrible accident.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>The Central Park Five</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjMxMDMyNzI1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTIxMDQ2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.599999904632568</score>
        <duration>119 min</duration>
        <launchDate>23 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Documentary</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Ken Burns Sarah Burns</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Antron McCray</star>
            <star>Kevin Richardson</star>
            <star>Kharey Wise</star>
        </stars>
        <description>In 1989, five black and Latino teenagers from Harlem were arrested and later convicted of raping a white woman in New York City's Central Park. They spent between 6 and 13 years in prison before a serial rapist confessed that he alone had committed the crime, leading to their convictions being overturned. Set against a backdrop of a decaying city beset by violence and racial tension, THE CENTRAL PARK FIVE tells the story of that horrific crime, the rush to judgment by the police, a media clamoring for sensational stories and an outraged public, and the five lives upended by this miscarriage of justice. Written by CP5</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Silver Linings Playbook</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM2MTI5NzA3MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODExNTc0OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.900000095367432</score>
        <duration>122 min</duration>
        <launchDate>25 December 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Romance</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>David O. Russell</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Bradley Cooper</star>
            <star>Jennifer Lawrence</star>
            <star>Robert De Niro</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Against medical advice and without the knowledge of her husband Pat Solatano Sr., caring Dolores Solatano discharges her adult son, Pat Solatano Jr., from a Maryland mental health institution after his minimum eight month court ordered stint. The condition of the release includes Pat Jr. moving back in with his parents in their Philadelphia home. Although Pat Jr.'s institutionalization was due to him beating up the lover of his wife Nikki, he was diagnosed with bipolar disorder. Nikki has since left him and has received a restraining order against him. Although he is on medication (which he doesn't take because of the way it makes him feel) and has mandatory therapy sessions, Pat Jr. feels like he can manage on the outside solely by healthy living and looking for the "silver linings" in his life. His goals are to get his old job back as a substitute teacher, but more importantly reunite with Nikki. He finds there are certain instances where he doesn't cope well, however no less so ... Written by Huggo</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Killing Them Softly</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODk3MDg2NDk5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjcxMjMzOA@@._V1_SY317_CR1,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.300000190734863</score>
        <duration>97 min</duration>
        <launchDate>30 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Crime</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Andrew Dominik</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Brad Pitt</star>
            <star>Ray Liotta</star>
            <star>Richard Jenkins</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Three amateurs stickup a Mob protected card game, causing the local criminal economy to collapse. Brad Pitt plays the hitman hired to track them down and restore order. Killing Them Softly also features Richard Jenkins , James Gandolfini, Ray Liotta, Scoot McNairy, Ben Mendelsohn, and Vincent Curatola. Max Casella, Trevor Long, Slaine and Sam Shepard also make appearances. Written by Anonymous</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>The Collection</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODQ0MDgzNDA0NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDM4MDQ1OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.0</score>
        <duration>82 min</duration>
        <launchDate>30 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Action</genre>
            <genre>Horror</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Marcus Dunstan</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Josh Stewart</star>
            <star>Emma Fitzpatrick</star>
            <star>Christopher McDonald</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Arkin escapes with his life from the vicious grips of "The Collector" during an entrapment party where he adds beautiful Elena to his "Collection." Instead of recovering from the trauma, Arkin is suddenly abducted from the hospital by mercenaries hired by Elena's wealthy father. Arkin is blackmailed to team up with the mercenaries and track down The Collector's booby trapped warehouse and save Elena. Written by Ryan Rodriguez</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Universal Soldier: Day of Reckoning</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM3ODMxMDY0MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDc3MTY0OA@@._V1_SY317_CR1,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.099999904632568</score>
        <duration>114 min</duration>
        <launchDate>25 October 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Action</genre>
            <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
            <genre>Thriller</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>John Hyams</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Jean-Claude Van Damme</star>
            <star>Dolph Lundgren</star>
            <star>Scott Adkins</star>
        </stars>
        <description>John awakens from a coma to discover his wife and daughter were slaughtered in a brutal home invasion. Haunted by images of the attack, he vows to kill the man responsible: Luc Deveraux. While John tries to piece his reality back together, things get more complicated when he is pursued by a relentless UniSol named Magnus. Meanwhile, Deveraux and surviving UniSol Andrew Scott are preparing to battle anarchy and build a new order ruled by Unisols without government oversight. They are weeding out the weak and constantly testing their strongest warriors in brutal, life-and-death combat. Luc has emerged operating the Unisol Church of Eventualism, taking in wayward Unisols whom the government has been secretly operating as remote-controlled sleeper agents. His mission is to liberate these Unisols from the implanted memories and the lies the government has inserted in them. As John gets closer to Deveraux and the rogue army of genetically enhanced warriors, he discovers more about himself ... Written by Anonymous</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Talaash</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTg5NzI3NzQzNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjM3MDU2OA@@._V1_SY317_CR2,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.300000190734863</score>
        <duration>131 min</duration>
        <launchDate>30 November 2012 (India)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Crime</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
            <genre>Mystery</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Reema Kagti</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Aamir Khan</star>
            <star>Kareena Kapoor</star>
            <star>Rani Mukerji</star>
        </stars>
        <description>The film opens with a car driving by the sea drive, which all of a sudden, screeches to a halt and turns randomly, to break the sidewalk, and fall into the sea. Next day, enter Inspector Surjan Singh Sekhawat, who is the investigating officer. A simultaneous plot reveals that he and his wife are coping with some personal loss of losing their only child, Karan. They have moved to their new home in Mumbai, where, his wife, Roshni is finishing with the unpacking. The doorbell rings, and she find out that it is an elderly lady, who introduces herself as Franny. She asks for some tea, and while Roshni is away into the kitchen, she rummages through the yet unpacked boxes, and finds a family photograph, where she addresses the dead child by his name, and seems happy. Meanwhile, Surjan encounters a sex worker named Rosie, who can shed some light upon the entire mystery. Written by debasree</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Dragon</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTc4OTUxMDQ1NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTczMDI2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.0</score>
        <duration>115 min</duration>
        <launchDate>31 October 2013 (Portugal)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Action</genre>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Peter Chan</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Donnie Yen</star>
            <star>Takeshi Kaneshiro</star>
            <star>Wei Tang</star>
        </stars>
        <description>A sinful martial arts expert wants to start a new tranquil life, only to be hunted by a determined detective and his former master.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>California Solo</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTk3MzQxMjExNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTY0NTE2OA@@._V1_SY317_CR1,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.400000095367432</score>
        <duration>94 min</duration>
        <launchDate>25 January 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Marshall Lewy</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Robert Carlyle</star>
            <star>Alexia Rasmussen</star>
            <star>Kathleen Wilhoite</star>
        </stars>
        <description>A former Britpop rocker who now works on a farm gets caught driving drunk and faces deportation after living in Los Angeles for many years. His efforts to stay in the U.S. force him to confront the past and current demons in his life.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Hecho en México</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjI1NTQ4MjkwMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDE4NTQ2OA@@._V1_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>5.800000190734863</score>
        <duration>98 min</duration>
        <launchDate>30 November 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Documentary</genre>
            <genre>History</genre>
            <genre>Music</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Duncan Bridgeman</director>
        <stars>
            <star>(not applicable)</star>
        </stars>
        <description>A documentary on some of contemporary Mexico's most iconic artists and performers.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Beware of Mr. Baker</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjIwNDE5NjE2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjY2ODc3OA@@._V1_SY317_CR0,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>7.0</score>
        <duration>100 min</duration>
        <launchDate>17 May 2013 (UK)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Documentary</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Jay Bulger</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Ginger Baker</star>
            <star>Femi Kuti</star>
            <star>Eric Clapton</star>
        </stars>
        <description>Ginger Baker looks back on his musical career with Cream and Blind Faith; his introduction to Fela Kuti; his self-destructive patterns and losses of fortune; and his current life inside a fortified South African compound.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Back to 1942</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjc2OTA3Mjc1Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjQyNzU3OA@@._V1_SY317_CR6,0,214,317_.jpg</image>
        <score>6.699999809265137</score>
        <duration>145 min</duration>
        <launchDate>29 November 2012 (China)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Drama</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>Xiaogang Feng</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Guoli Zhang</star>
            <star>Daoming Chen</star>
            <star>Xuejian Li</star>
        </stars>
        <description>A deadly drought in 1942 takes its toll on central China's Henan province during the war against Japan.</description>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <name>Addicted to Fame</name>
        <image>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkxOTk1NTIwNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODAzNjQ1OA@@._V1._CR75,74.16667175292969,1014,1502.9999542236328_SX214_.jpg</image>
        <score>2.799999952316284</score>
        <duration>89 min</duration>
        <launchDate>19 March 2012 (USA)</launchDate>
        <genres>
            <genre>Documentary</genre>
            <genre>Biography</genre>
            <genre>Comedy</genre>
        </genres>
        <director>David Giancola</director>
        <stars>
            <star>Anna Nicole Smith</star>
            <star>David Giancola</star>
            <star>John James</star>
        </stars>
        <description>The hilarious, outrageous, and ultimately tragic true story of one filmmaker's seduction into moral blindness in the glare of the media spotlight. What begins innocently is a film that seems nothing more than a "Behind-the-Scenes" tell-all, but Filmmaker David Giancola has larger issues in mind and the film quickly takes a dark turn. Giancola uses his tale as a modern parable about the dangers of celebrity and it's debilitating effect upon our society. Back in 2005, he wanted to break out by making a "Movie that mocked B-Movies". He thought he could manipulate the media by casting Anna Nicole Smith. In the end the media manipulated him instead as his star and one of his producers died in a media feeding frenzy. The film bombed, but the story was one of the most reported events of 2007, behind only coverage of the Iraq war. The truth is always stranger and more unbelievable than fiction... Filmmaker Giancola spent over three years in editing from over 80 Hours of never-before seen ... Written by Susan Potter Publicity</description>
    </movie>
</movie_list>

